<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Magical Balls</string>

    <string name="jouer">Play</string>
    <string name="rouler">Roll</string>
    <string name="commencer">Start</string>
    <string name="recommencer">Restart</string>
    <string name="Continuer">Continuer</string>
    <string name="confirmation">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="oui">Yes</string>
    <string name="non">Nso</string>
    <string name="endurance">Stamina</string>
    <string name="force">Strenght</string>
    <string name="agilite">Agility</string>
    <string name="intelligence">Intelligence</string>

    <string name="descriptionCombat1">"x roll : y</string>
    <string name="descriptionCombat3">x attack</string>
    <string name="descriptionCombat4">x loose y points</string>
    <string name="combatGagnant">You win !</string>
    <string name="combatPerdant">You loose :(</string>
    <string name="combatFin">"Click on roll to continue"</string>

    <string name="descriptionApp">
        This is a story about a little sad guy. One day, he called upon a big dragon,
        wishing he could grant him his wish: to finally be happy.
        To do so, he will have to gather all 3 sacred crystals: the crystal of health, the crystal of wealth and the crystal of love.
        He will have to get through difficult tests to get there.
    </string>
    <string name="description1">
        The crystal of wealth is guarded by the troll of the donjon.
        It would be wise to go get the donjon\'s map to not get lost in these multiple corridors.
    </string>
    <string name="description2">
        You will find te map in the small village\'s market.
        To fnd the donjon\'s monster, you will need to make your way through intersections
        respecting the following sequence: Right, Left, Left, Right
        Are you ready to defeat the donjon\'s troll?
    </string>
    <string name="description4">
        In this forest, you will come face to face with the forest\'s troll.
        You have now the opportunity to get the crystal of love, although,
        you are second guessing your ability to win the fight.
    </string>
    <string name="description6">
        The lake\'s troll is the one who has the crystal of health.
        You will need to face him on his own territory. Without this gems you can say goodbye
        a happy life.
        Are you ready to face the lake\'s troll?
    </string>
    <string name="description8">
        Congratulalions. The balls never existed. It was a scam.
        You can not find happiness. It is already in you.
        You only need to be able to recognize it.
    </string>
    <string name="descriptionMort">
        You are dead. Failing to find the 3 magical balls,
        left you in a state of despair, loneliness and poverty
        I few days later yo died from an unknown sickness.
    </string>

    <string name="seBattre">Fight</string>
    <string name="fuir">Flee</string>
    <string name="carte">Map</string>
    <string name="mourir">Die</string>
    <string name="rejouer">Replay</string>
    <string name="quitter">Quit</string>
    <string name="commencerCombat">Click on roll to start the battle</string>
    <string name="erreurNom">"!!! You must have a name to create your character !!!"</string>
    <string name="erreurStat">"!!! You must generate your statistics create your character !!!"</string>
    <string name="erreurStat2">"You've reached the maximum amount of generation possible"</string>
    <string name="monPerso">My character</string>
    <string name="générer">Generate stat</string>
    <string name="créer">Create character</string>
    <string name="choisir">Choose an Adventure</string>
    <string name="scroll">Scroll to see more</string>
    <string name="erreurConnexion">You are not connected. Connect yourself to get new aventures</string>
</resources>